roceteer.com 2017-03-02

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy ("Agreement") 

#### This Agreement was last modified on September 9, 2014.

ROCeteer (â€œROCeteer,â€ â€œwe,â€ â€œus,â€ or â€œourâ€) created this Privacy Policy inform you about how the information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of ROCeteer in connection with our website located at www.ROCeteer.com (the â€œSiteâ€) and the online service (the â€œServiceâ€) which is available to you through the Site.

By visiting the Site and/or using the Service, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings set forth in our Terms of Use.

###### Information We Collect

We do not collect any personal information from you unless you voluntarily provide it to us.

When you apply to be a Mentee or Cloud Roceteer, you will be asked to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, and email address, biographical information, company information including but not limited to revenue, headcount and services provided by your company. You will also have the option to provide us with your headshot or other photographs that you choose to use in connection with your profile. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to this information as â€œPersonal Information.â€ If you choose to make any profile or any User Generated Content publicly available through the Service, then you acknowledge and agree that such information is made available to other users of the Service and is not subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Like most web sites, we use automatic data collection technology when you visit the Site to record information that identifies your computer, to track your use of the Site, and to collect certain basic information about you and your surfing habits. This information includes information about your operating system, your IP addresses, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, keywords, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of a website you visit, and similar information concerning your use of the Site and the Service (the â€œUsage Informationâ€). We collect this Usage Information by using cookies and pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs). Cookies are small packets of data that a web site stores on your computerâ€™s hard drive so that your computer will â€œrememberâ€ information about your visit. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web site users. You can reject cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet providerâ€™s â€œhelpâ€ file. If you reject cookies, you may still visit the Site, but may not be able to use some areas of the Site. We do not collect Personal Information in this way, but if youâ€™ve provided us with Personal Information we may associate that information with the information that is collected automatically. Automatic data collection may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.

We may also allow third-party companies that are presenting advertisements on the Site to set and access their own cookies. Such third-party cookies are not governed by this Privacy Policy, but by the privacy policies of such third party.

###### Use of Your Information; Opt-Out Procedure

We will use your Personal Information and Usage Information for the following purposes: 

  * To respond to your requests and to provide you with the Service; 
  * To respond to your inquiries and contact you about changes to the Site, and/or the Service; 
  * To send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like) regarding products or services you are receiving, and for billing and collection purposes; 
  * To improve the Site and/or the Service; 
  * For any other purposes disclosed at the time the information is collected or to which you consent; and 
  * As otherwise specifically described in this Privacy Policy. 

We may analyze your Personal Information in aggregate form which does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, advertisers, manufacturers and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

We may disclose Personal Information to third party marketers (who may combine such Personal Information with their own records, and records available from other sources), for their own direct marketing purposes, and the direct marketing purposes of other third party marketers. If you wish to opt-out of sharing your Personal Information with third party marketers for their own and third party direct marketing purposes, please send a message to us here.

We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases, hosting services, and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function, which may include Personal Information.

If we or all or substantially all of our assets are acquired, we expect that the information that we have collected, including Personal Information, would be transferred along with our other business assets. 

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is or may be causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Service, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. 

###### How We Protect Your Information

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. In particular, e-mail sent to or from us may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

###### Links

The Site and the Service may contain content, services, advertising and other materials that link to web sites operated by third parties. We have no control over those other sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them.

###### Important Notice to Non-U.S. Residents

The Site and the Service are operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer.

###### Children

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 through the Site and/or the Service. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their childrenâ€™s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide Personal Information through any website without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

###### California Privacy Rights

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to obtain certain information about the types of Personal Information that companies with whom they have an established business relationship (and that are not otherwise exempt) have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, including the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. To submit a request pursuant to Section 1798.83, please send us a message via compliance@roceteer.com

###### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on the Site as soon as they go into effect. By accessing the Site and/or using the Service after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

###### How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please send us a message via privacy@roceteer.com
